I won a snack from the event
very good
and 1 lot of candy also from Minas
Cara Minas is very good in sweet
is on
I opened 1 question box
when I was Ali at the airport bro
and then I received 1 very strong review like this from 1 Guy
how can i say
I opened Instagram
and then there was a message from a heavy guy so you know
1 good opportunity appears for you
then the person speaks
no no brother
it's wrong
stay with the motorcycle and go deliver
passes perrengue even
it's something that bothers me a little
not for me
not even what you think of me
but what are you thinking of yourself
within that limiting speed
of thinking you can't man
so if you can't
it's not fair the other follow you know
the right thing is for you to stay in the sun selling truffle
the right thing is for you to keep
in the low
because you can't dream you can't look at 1 car
of the time
and want
You can't look at 1 book on the shelf of 1
airport and talk
caraca hand
1 day I want to have my book there too
when you conquer something
will say it's privilege
which is cool luck
I built something that will please you
but business is mine
he needs to pull me bag
if you have the opportunity to do more
I will do more
and it's not wrong
you know what's wrong
not be honest
it's not wrong to dedicate yourself
it's wrong to be jealous of the charts
and not run after your dream
my brother
while you're out there sticking your dick in
I have a look here running after my uncle
we're together we're going
I will rest 1 little
and tomorrow I promise
that I return the videos in the best way
no way i am answering 1 hater
that's not it Man
but trying to help 1
1 thought
that is wrong
especially for people who are in battle
it's in the fight
who thinks we don't deserve it
and today was the fifty
I confess to you that I'm super tired
is on
sorry ok
You never Gonna get my love